## Catherine Elizabeth Havird

Los Angeles, CA | (858) 276-8625 | lizhavird1@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/elizabeth-havird-1649a267/ | https://github.com/lizhavird | elizabethhavird.herokuapp.com

# **Professional Summary**

As a lady of southern hospitality, I exhibit excellent customer service and an integral work ethic by nature. I am dependable and highly regard my word. With 4+ years experience in the fashion industry, I have discovered my affinity for bringing people's visions to life. I bring this same affinity into both front and back end development.

## Work Experience

Intern, April 2020-Present

Victorise - San Diego, CA

Developed and debugged mobile application using react-native, xcode, github, and sourcetree...

Developed and debugged web application using ionic, nodejs, mongodb, robo 3T, github/sourcetree, and angularJS.

Practiced paired programming and loved it!

Student, January 2020 - May 2020

Learn Academy - San Diego, CA

Attended a 580 hour, 4 month, intensive bootcamp, covering topics/languages such as Ruby on Rails, React, Javascript, Github, HTML/CSS, SQL, and Jest.

Developed web applications, practicing paired/mob programming, implementing responsive designs, utilizing both front and back end development.

Examples of the applications developed can be found here: <a href="https://github.com/lizhavird">https://github.com/lizhavird</a>

Manager of Photography, August 2015-March 2020

#### **Buca Di Beppo** - San Diego, CA

Gained confidence in my ability to sell a product or idea, meeting or exceeding daily sales goals. I also gained a thick skin for rejection.

Learned about oversight of employees, and inspiring our team members with the spirit of sales.

Gained technical photography skills, as well as a familiarity with Photoshop.

Fashion Model, Febuary 2015 - February 2018

#### IMG Worldwide

Portrayed designers ideas through visual advertising/fashion shows.

Integrated myself into different communities around the world, building relationships with designers, photographers, and agents.

Learned how to practice self discipline and form new habits, following a rigorous diet and exercise routine.

### Education

High School Graduate: La Jolla High School - June 2015

Member of Madrigals Choir and Varsity Cheerleading.